ูุง ู ุทุงุญ ุญุธู ูุง ูู
HELL NO
ุญุฒูู ุจุณ ุฏูุนู ูู ุณุงุฆู
ุงุตุญุงุจู ููุซุฑ ููุง ุงุฌุงูู
ููุณู ุจููุณู ุฏูู ุดุงูู
ุฅู ููุชู  ุชุจุบููู ุ
ูุง Baby ูู Baby ุชูุงุบููู !
ุฎูู ูุนุงู ูุญูุงุชู ูู ..
ุชุฑู ุฏููู ูุฏููู !!
ุนู ุญูุงุชู ูุง ุชุณุฃู
ุบููุถ ููู ููุง ุจุชููู
ูุฑุฏุฉ ูู ููุชู ุฑุงุญ ุชุฐุจู
ุนูุฒููู ุจุณ ูุง ุชุญุจููู
ูุงู ุทุงุญ ุญุธู ูุงูู
HELL NO
ุญุฒูู ุจุณ ุฏูุนู ูู ุณุงุฆู
ุงุตุญุงุจู ููุซุฑ ููุง ุฃุฌุงูู
ููุณู ุจููุณู ุฏูู ุดุงูู
Round and round
Tโs  simple man for her
Not a love
but still can be best friends
Youโre my soul
Not a hoe
Call me  a boo
Ur angle in this world
Beautiful
She made me lose my mind
Im a fan
Behind ur back god demn
Baby girl
Donโt be alone
I said im the one
Now text me if u home
Round and round
Tโs simple man for her
Ur angle in this world
Baby girl
Donโt be alone
Now text me if u home
Story with ูููู but no ููุณ
You my number one still called my ace
its a bad luck we met at this place
In a fucked up point named new FEJS
Why you so late
Heart โค๏ธ and the brain ๐ง
having a debate
Trying to win
the key to the gate
Look at my plate
Full of depression surrounded with hate
So much shit for me to handle
Too many people for me to cancel
No enough space for me ti gamble
Devil ๐ฟ on me says she is an angel
Impossible mission
nigga gotta have Tom Cruise vision
The clock is ticking
Big black shades sand storm hitting
Round and round
Tโs  simple man for her
Not a love
but still can be best friends
Youโre my soul
Not a hoe
Call me  a boo
Ur angle in this world
Beautiful
She made me lose my mind
Im a fan
Behind ur back god demn
Baby girl
Donโt be alone
I said im the one
Now text me if u home
Round and round
Tโs simple man for her
Ur angle in this world
Baby girl
Donโt be alone
Now text me if u home
ูุงู ุทุงุญ ุญุธู ูุงูู
HELL NO
ุญุฒูู ุจุณ ุฏูุนู ูู ุณุงุฆู
ุงุตุญุงุจู ููุซุฑ ููุง ุฃุฌุงูู
ููุณู ุจููุณู ุฏูู ุดุงูู
ุงุณุฃู ุถููุฑู
ูุง ูุฑุถู ุจุงููุฐุจุฉ ุชุนูููู
ูุงูุบุดู ููุจู ูุชุดููููู !
ููุงู
ุดูุทุงู ุงูุง ุงุญุฐุฑููู .
ูุง ุชุตุฏููุฉ ูู ูุงู ูู
ุจูุนุทููู ูู ูุง ูู
ุดูุทุงูู ูููู ุฐุงูู
ูุงู
Baby
It's OK
I'm here
ุฏูู Love
do not Cry
ุงุตุฏูุงุก ูุน ุจุนุถ ููุฃุจุฏ
ูุงู ุทุงุญ ุญุธู ูุงูู
HELL NO
ุญุฒูู ุจุณ ุฏูุนู ูู ุณุงุฆู
ุงุตุญุงุจู ููุซุฑ ููุง ุฃุฌุงูู
ููุณู ุจููุณู ุฏูู ุดุงูู